{\clip(190,219,190,219)\t(0,600,\clip(100,217,280,220))\t(16600,17100,\clip(190,217,190,220))}m 0 0 m 180 1 l 0 1 l 0 0 l 180 0
{\clip(80,220,300,220)\t(0,600,\clip(80,197,300,240))\t(3700,4200,\clip(80,220,300,220))}翻\h译
ainomiadue\hBeraa\h01Iris
Tabs\hDentonWei\hKKKwn
{\clip(80,220,300,220)\t(0,600,\clip(80,197,300,240))\t(3700,4200,\clip(80,220,300,220))}校对\h&\h后期
魔鬼无情暴力锅\h\h\h\h你以为列
{\clip(80,220,300,220)\t(0,600,\clip(80,197,300,240))\t(3700,4200,\clip(80,220,300,220))}总监
大红
片头推广合作洽谈\h请联系普罗米修斯邮箱\hPLMXS2016@GmaiL.com
♪ 梦中佳人 ♪
♪ Beautiful dreamer ♪
♪ 为我醒来 ♪
♪ Wake unto me ♪
♪ 星光和露珠 ♪
♪ Starlight and dewdrops ♪
♪ 都在等你 ♪
♪ Are waiting for thee ♪
♪ 无礼世界的声音 ♪
♪ Sounds of the rude world ♪
♪ 在白天听到 ♪
♪ Heard in the day ♪
救命
Help!
♪ 在月光下入睡 ♪
♪ Lulled by the moonlight ♪
♪ 万物消散 ♪
♪ Have all passed away ♪
♪ 梦中佳人 ♪
♪ Beautiful dreamer ♪
♪ 我歌中的皇后 ♪
♪ Queen of my song ♪
♪ 记下我追求你时 ♪
♪ List' while I woo thee ♪
♪ 那些温柔的旋律 ♪
♪ With soft melody ♪
失\n踪\n女\n孩
♪ 忙碌生活的烦恼 ♪
♪ Gone are the cares ♪
♪ 都已消失 ♪
♪ Of life's busy throng ♪
一个美国的未解之谜
♪ 梦中佳人 ♪
♪ Beautiful dreamer ♪
♪ 为我醒来 ♪
♪ Awake unto me ♪
你是耍我吗
Ah, are you shitting me?
我跟你说过  我需要更多工时
I told you I need more hours.
这周你只给我排了3天班
You only got me on the schedule three days this week.
乔勒都有5天的班  搞什么鬼
Joelle has five. What the hell, man?
乔勒进门时会微笑
Joelle smiles when she comes in the door.
她肯定不止做了这点事
Yeah, bet that's not all she does.
天啊
Jeez.
艾伦维尔  纽约  2010
你好
Hello?
吉尔伯特女士  请来接你女儿
Mrs. Gilbert, pick up your daughter.
-她被停课到周四  -什么叫被停课
- She's suspended till Thursday. - What do you mean suspended?
厕所里发生了意外
There was an incident in the bathroom.
-她有伤人吗  -等你过来  再跟你解释
- Did she hurt anybody? - We'll explain when you come here.
-你吃药了吗  -没
- You take your medicine? - No.
我不喜欢那个药  它让我犯困
I don't like that stuff. It makes me sleepy.
它也能防止你
It also keeps you from lighting paper towels on fire
在女厕所里点纸巾
in the girls' bathroom.
你到底在想什么
What the hell were you thinking?
我们晚点再说这事
We're gonna talk about this later.
闯了祸就要承担
There are gonna be consequences.
还不错
Not bad.
一个球员拿到了高额工资
...player gets a top salary,
下一个球员就想拿到更高的工资
the next player negotiates for even higher.
他们必须选择一条路
They have to go one direction or another.
不能总是改来改去的
You can't be half-pregnant.
拿好你能得到的工资
You've got a salary cap that you enforce,
要么就干脆走人
or you can just go wild.
是这样的
That's true. Well...
-妈  -珊楠
- Hey, Mom. - Hey, Shannan.
终于联系到你了
Hey. Oh, glad I finally got you.
刚刚还想到你呢
Was thinking about you.
-你怎么样  -又在天堂过了一天呗
- How's it going? - You know, just another day in paradise.
-什么意思  -我老板就是个混蛋
- What do you mean? - My boss is a total asshole.
-把我的轮班给了新来的女孩  -混蛋
- Gave one of my shifts to the new girl. - What a dick.
-是啊  -你需要的话我可以给你一些钱
- Yeah. - I can find some cash if you need it.
你愿意给  真是太好了
Well, that's really nice of you to offer.
-我回头还你  -我知道
- I'll pay you back. - I know you will.
等我撑过这段时间
You know, just as soon as I get on the other side of this shit.
-好  -已经好几周了
- Okay. - It's been a couple weeks.
-我可以明天晚上回来吗  -当然
- Can I come up tomorrow night? - Yes!
-你当然可以明天回家  -太好了
- Yes, you can come home tomorrow! - Awesome.
-姑娘们会很兴奋的  -我也是  等不及了
- Oh, the girls will be so excited. - Me, too. Can't wait.
明天见  宝贝
We'll see you tomorrow, baby.
-再见  -好
- Bye. - Great.
1999年  珊楠才艺表演
♪ 梦中佳人 ♪
♪ Beautiful dreamer ♪
♪ 为我醒来 ♪
♪ Wake unto me ♪
♪ 星光和露珠 ♪
♪ Starlight and dewdrops ♪
♪ 都在等你 ♪
♪ Are waiting for thee ♪
♪ 无礼世界的声音 ♪
♪ Sounds of the rude world... ♪
-嘿  -嘿  舍尔
- Hey. - Hey, Sherre.
珊楠回来吃晚饭
Shannan's coming for dinner.
你说什么就是什么
If you say so.
♪ 梦中佳人 ♪
♪ Beautiful dreamer ♪
♪ 我歌中的皇后 ♪
♪ Queen of my song ♪
♪ 记下我追求你时 ♪
♪ List' while I woo thee... ♪
妈  是你让她回来的
Mom, did you ask her to come
-还是她想回来  -没人需要问
- or was it her idea? - No one has to ask.
这里还是她的家
This is still her home.
我还是她的妈妈  我们还是她的家人
I'm still her mom and we're still her family.
我在想  我们可以在晚饭后
I'm thinking maybe we'll watch
看那个才艺表演的视频
that talent show video after dinner.
我觉得她会喜欢的
I think she'd get a kick out of that.
怎么了
What?
没事
Nothing.
你就不能高兴一次吗
Why can't you be happy for once?
也许她有工作要做
Maybe she had to work.
她昨晚也说有工作
She worked last night.
这是珊楠  我现在没空接电话
This is Shannan. I can't answer my phone now
因为我在忙更有趣的事情
because I'm doing something way more fun.
嘿  迪瓦
Hey, Diva.
我知道你不是故意的  但是妈妈很伤心
Look, I know you didn't mean it, but I think Mom's really hurt.
尽管她永远也不会承认
Even though she'll never admit it.
你应该打给她  然后道歉
You should call her and apologize.
还有  你男朋友打来了
Also, your boyfriend called.
不管怎样
Anyway...
我想你了  迪瓦
I miss you, Diva.
北萨纳克社区学院
-昨晚的事我很抱歉  -抱歉什么
- Sorry about last night. - For what?
我知道你很期待珊楠回家
Well, I know you were looking forward to Shannan coming home.
没事
It's fine.
-你今天洗澡吗  -别管我
- Gonna get your butt in the shower today? - Leave me alone.
-你确定你还好吗  -上帝啊
- Are you sure you're okay? - For Christ's sakes!
世界不会因为珊楠有时间冲突而到头
The world's not gonna end 'cause Shannan had a schedule conflict.
你好
Hello.
谁
Who?
该死的
Goddamn it.
你是谁
Who is this?
你怎么拿到这个号码的
Uh, how did you get this number?
我不知道你为什么要问我
Well, I don't know why you're asking me.
她12岁以后就不在这儿住了
She hasn't lived here since she's 12.
假如她欠你钱了  那你找错人了
So, if she owes you money, you're barking up the wrong flagpole.
-是谁  -某个医生
- Who is it? - Some doctor.
几点了  该死  要迟到了
What time is it? Oh, shit, I'm late.
他想知道  我有没有见过珊楠
He wanted to know if I'd seen Shannan.
珊楠的男朋友昨晚打给我
Shannan's boyfriend called me last night,
问我知不知道她在哪儿
asking if I knew where she was.
我以为他们只是吵架了
I thought they were just in a fight.
我试着打了5次电话
I've tried her five times, and each time
但每次都进到语音信箱了
it's gone straight to voicemail.
妈
Mom.
他之前从没打给过我
He's never called me before.
我相信没事  等她几天就好了
I'm sure it's fine. Give it a day.
她会打来的
She'll call.
你的手怎么了
What happened to your hand?
-你的手怎么了  -烫到了
- What happened to your hand? - I burned it.
都48小时了  你们什么时候开始找呢
It's been 48 hours. When will you start looking?
找我女儿
For my daughter.
在吗  还在吗
Hello? Hello?
-他们挂断了  -他们根本不去找她吗
- They hung up. - They're not even looking for her?
他们说系统里没有她的立案
They can't find her in the system.
那  那个医生呢
What about that doctor?
在来电显示上应该有他的号码
His number should be on the caller ID.
显示的是未知
It came up "unknown."
他说他在长岛
He said he was in Long Island.
也许我们应该打电话给医院
Maybe we should start calling the hospitals.
长岛有上百家医院
There are hundreds of hospitals on Long Island.
是珊楠出事了吗
Did something happen to Shannan?
纽约  泽西城
一名在长岛的医生打给了我
A doctor on Long Island called me.
我会把她加到系统里的  女士
I'll put her in the system, ma'am.
走吧  姑娘们
Come on, girls.
对不起  除非她现在就在您身边
I'm sorry, but unless she's physically here with you,
否则我无法提供任何信息
I can't give you any information.
没人知道她在哪儿  而且警察什么都没做
Nobody knows where she is, and the police haven't done a thing.
无论如何  我都要得到这些电话记录
Now, one way or another, I am leaving with those phone records.
如果你不愿意帮我
If you're you're not going to help me,
找个愿意的人来
go get me someone who will.
-她有5个  -5个什么
- She has five. - Five what?
5个电话
Five cellphones.
妈  为什么珊楠需要5部电话
Mom, why would Shannan need five phones?
你知道他男朋友住哪儿吗
Do you know where this boyfriend lives?
你最后一次见到她  是什么时候
Okay, so when did you last see her?
她去长岛工作  然后就再没回来
So, she went to work in Long Island and never came back.
想知道更多吗  去问她的司机
Wanna know more? Ask her driver.
好吗  他才是应该把她带回来的人
Okay? He was the one that was supposed to bring her back.
珊楠在长岛做什么
What was Shannan doing in Long Island?
卖女童子军饼干  你以为呢
Selling Girl Scout cookies. What you think?
你不如省点时间  说说你对她做了什么
Why don't you save time and tell us what you did to her?
我是不会伤害她的
I would never hurt her.
那你为什么打她
Then why'd you hit her so hard she had to have
打到要在下巴上接钛板
a titanium plate grafted into her jaw?
你一点都不了解我  小姑娘
You don't know shit about me, little girl.
你肯定也不了解珊楠
And you sure as shit don't know about Shannan.
你拿了她给你的钱和礼物
You take the money and the gifts that she buys you,
你都不问问这些都是从哪儿来的
and you don't think to ask where it all comes from?
你们以为
And when she comes home,
她是为了谁回家的
who do you think she's coming home to?
我一直在她身边
I was always there for her.
你们有吗
Were you?
去哪儿能找到这个司机
Where can I find this driver?
你们俩在这儿等着
You two wait here.
妈  我不能让你一个人进去
Mom, I'm not letting you go in there alone.
锁好门  我们就去一会儿
Lock the doors. We'll only be a minute.
我带电话了
I have my phone.
我在找珊楠·吉尔伯特  我是她母亲
I'm looking for Shannan Gilbert. I'm her mother.
你是她的司机迈克尔·白  对吧
You're Michael Pak, right? Her driver.
你需要放松点  女士
You need to relax, lady.
她在哪儿
Where is she?
我们去了橡树海滩
We went out to Oak Beach.
她进去见了一个人
She went in to see a guy.
出来的时候就崩溃了  明白吗
Next thing, she's freaking out, okay?
发生了什么
What happened?
我只是个司机
I'm just a driver.
我不进去
I don't go in.
我等在车里然后接她回家  我只做这些
I wait in my car and then I drive her home. That's all I do.
-你只做这些  -是
- That's all you do? - Yeah.
但你没有把她送回家
Yeah, well, you didn't take her home.
那天晚上你女儿情绪非常激动
Your daughter was hysterical that night.
她沿着公路跑
She ran down the road,
敲了所有开着灯的房子的门
banging on the door of any house with a light on.
她神志不清
She wasn't making any sense,
喊着胡言乱语
she was shouting all kinds of gibberish.
我试图帮她
I tried to help her.
但她不让我帮  所以我就不干了
But she wouldn't let me, so I said fuck it.
他妈的
Oh, fuck.
橡树海滩
Oak Beach?
沿着海洋公园路往前  经过琼斯海滩
Way down Ocean Parkway, past Jones Beach.
是个封闭的社区  附近几公里都没有人烟
It's a gated community. Miles from anything.
纽约  长岛
这是我们的最后一次联系
This is the last contact we had.
珊楠
注意安全
一定
你住在艾伦维尔  你女儿住在泽西城
If you live in Ellenville and your daughter lives in Jersey City,
那你们为什么要来萨福克县呢
what the hell are you guys doing here in Suffolk County, hmm?
她的通话记录里都是来自631区的电话
Well, her phone records are full of calls from a 631 area code.
你们填过失踪人员报告表了吗
Have you filed a Missing Persons report?
我们联系过泽西城  他们没有记录
Just phoned Jersey City, they don't have a record of it.
-妈  我不舒服  -稍等一下
- Mom, I don't feel so good. - Just a second.
她仅仅是没回家
Just because she didn't come home,
不等于情况很糟糕
it doesn't mean it's a five-alarm fire now.
对吗
Right?
那为什么她最后的通话记录
Okay. Then why was her last contact with anyone is
是打给911的一通23分钟的电话
a 23-minute phone call to 911?
-你好  -珊楠  快上车
- Hello? - Shannan, get in the car!
快点  你在干嘛
Come on, what are you doing?
小姐  你不说你在哪  我没办法帮你
Miss, I can't help if you don't tell me where you are.
怎么回事
What's wrong?
我真的没法识别你的位置
I'm having a hard time getting a read on your location.
快些  珊楠  回来
Come on, Shannan! Come back!
救救我  救命
Help me! Help!
好了
All right, um...
报告上说小队在5点40分到达
The report says the unit arrived at 5:40.
警官询问过一些住户
Officers interviewed several residents who said they...
他们说看到你女儿是独自离开的
saw your daughter leave on her own
没有出现什么  可疑迹象
with no sign of, um... suspicious activity.
这是她的夹克
This is her jacket.
是的  从那通报警电话拨打的地方
Yeah, well, as far as the 911 call goes,
那些住户说她当时磕了药
the residents say that she was on drugs.
我女儿不嗑药
My daughter doesn't do drugs.
您和您女儿关系亲密吗  吉尔伯特夫人
You got a close relationship with her, Ms. Gilbert?
你说什么
Excuse me?
你知道她半夜在离家160多公里的
What was she doing in a gated community,
封闭社区里做了些什么吗
100 miles away from home in the middle of the night?
恕我在这直言
Can I be frank here with you just for a minute, please?
当像这样的女孩失踪时
When girls like this go missing,
她处于一个高风险的环境
it's a high-risk environment.
你懂的  我是说  也许她是离家出走
You know, I mean, maybe she ran away,
也许某一天她就回来了
maybe she'll turn up.
喂  你可以消停一会吗
Hey. Do you think you could stop that
就一会  好吗  甜心
for one second, please, sweetheart?
就一会
Just one.
我女儿没有嗑药
My daughter isn't on drugs.
她也没有离家出走  她是失踪了
She didn't run away. She's missing.
到现在为止  我被警方电话挂断过
Now, I have been hung up on,
当面敷衍过  无视过
dismissed, and ignored,
但这件事  我不会息事宁人
but one thing I won't be is silenced.
现在你说我女儿不是失踪  行
Now, you say she's not missing. Fine.
那是你的立场  但我的立场是
That's your position, but here's mine.
她在4点51分打电话报警
She called for help at 4:51,
但你们警方5点40分才到
and you arrived at 5:40.
从接到报警电话到出警
How in the fuck does it take an hour
中间他妈的要用一个小时吗
to respond to a call like that?
天
Jesus.
打开车窗
Crack a window.
吉尔戈海滩至橡树海滩一段的
Ocean Parkway is shut down
海洋公园路现已关闭
between Gilgo Beach and Oak Beach.
警方尚未透露太多有关信息
Police aren't saying much,
目前已知的是
but what we do know is that
一名警官带着警犬
a police dog picked up a scent
在搜寻一桩失踪案时
and a canine officer,
搜寻到了现场
knowing there was a Missing Persons report,
随后搜查队介入
brought in a search team.
我们期望在今晚
We expect to learn more tonight
萨福克县警察局局长
when Suffolk County Police Commissioner,
理查德·多默
Richard Dormer,
主持的新闻发布会上获取更多信息
holds a press conference.
多默局长于今年早些时候
Commissioner Dormer made news
曾因在一次
earlier this year
因警员问题进行的罢免投票中险胜
after narrowly surviving a vote of dismissal
而引起关注
for staffing level issues
此次投票可能与三名投票者的死亡有关
that may have contributed to the deaths of three voters.
-你好  -你好
- Hey. - Hey.
一共发现了四具尸体
There's four in all.
都是骸骨
They're skeletal.
被麻布包裹着
They're wrapped in burlap.
并且  尸体被均匀分开摆放了
And they're, uh... They're spaced evenly apart.
一具在这后边
There's... one down there,
这里  这里
here, here,
还有那边
and over there.
如果媒体们报道出
If the press starts to say
我们正在调查一桩连环杀人案
we got a serial killer on our hands,
舆论会爆炸的  控制住局面  理查德
this will blow up. Keep this under control, Richard,
不然你就可以早点退休回家了
or your retirement could come sooner
比你原想的早  懂了吗
than you planned. You got it?
-明白了  长官  -好的  处理好
- Okay, sir. - All right, go handle it.
谢谢您
Thank you.
去他妈的
Jesus fucking Christ.
多默局长  长官
Commissioner Dormer, sir,
媒体准备好了
they're ready for you.
局长  长官  请看这边  谢谢
Commissioner! Sir, over here, please. Thanks.
-长官  看这边  -在搜寻一名失踪妓女时
- Sir, over here. - While searching for a missing prostitute,
我们的一位警官在海洋公园路旁边
one of our officers has located...
发现了四具尸体
four bodies in an area along Ocean Parkway.
所有尸体是被同一人抛尸的吗
Were the bodies all left there by the same person?
目前无法判断
I can't say that.
虽然这是一桩不同寻常的案件
This is an anomaly. There's...
但无需恐慌
There's no need for panic.
我要说的就是这些  谢谢
That's all I have to say. Thank you.
长官  我们还有一个问题  长官
Sir, we do have one more...Sir
艾伦维尔餐厅
Ellenville Diner.
我需要你替我今晚的班
Hey. I need you to cover for me tonight.
-为什么  发生什么事了  -我必须要回去
- Why? What happened? - I gotta go back.
回哪里  长岛吗  为珊楠的事吗
Where? Long Island, for Shannan?
是的  去警局  他们发现了尸体
Yeah, the police station, they found bodies.
天哪  其他女孩知道了吗
Oh, God. Do the girls know?
我正准备跟她们说
Yeah, I'm about to tell them now.
好的  别担心代班的事
Of course. Don't worry about it.
我会搞定的  好运
I got you. Good luck.
-好的  谢了  我欠你一次  -再见
- Okay, thanks. I owe you. - Bye.
我们要回萨福克县了
We gotta go back to Suffolk County.
妈  怎么了
Mom, what's going on?
妈
Mom?
警方不会在电话里  告诉你发生了什么
They don't tell you that over the phone.
当行动组进入调查时  她已是不见了
When the units rolled up, she's a ghost.
周围住户看起来对此反应非常冷淡
Residents seemed pretty calm about it.
一切看起来都还好
Everything seemed to be kosher.
他们认为这是一起家庭内部纷争
They figured that it was a domestic disturbance
会自然地内部解决的
which resolved itself.
关于橡树海滩  你了解多少
What do you know about Oak Beach?
我知道一伙人喜欢  时不时地在那开派对
I know the guys like to go to parties out there once in a while.
为什么  是哪种派对
Why? What kind of parties?
理查德  你知道的  像生日聚会
Oh, come on, Richard, you know. Birthdays,
少年礼  青年礼一类的  你懂的
bar mitzvahs, quinceañeras, come on. You know.
-你以为这是在开玩笑吗  -没有
- You think this is some kind of joke? - No. I don't.
听着  她又不是在我的后备箱里
Look... she's not in my fucking trunk.
外面那个才是真的麻烦
Your real problem is that one out there.
她很难缠
She's feisty.
知道了
Okay.
我来处理
Let me handle it.
好的  女士们  请跟我来  这边走
Okay, ladies, come with me, please. This way.
快来  走吧
Come on. Let's go.
吉尔伯特夫人
Mrs. Gilbert.
感谢你这么快赶过来
Thank you for coming so quickly. I'm...
多默局长
I'm Commissioner Dormer.
-我知道你开了很久车  -有她的尸体吗
- I know it was a long drive - Are any of them her?
目前没有
It appears not.
但是在我们谈话的同时
But we are working a grid
也正在进行区域网格式搜寻
as we speak.
明早我们会首先开始空中搜寻
Tomorrow morning we begin the aerial searches, first thing.
那是推断她  你会全部搜寻一遍  对吗
That's assuming she's... You're searching everywhere, right?
我想问你一些有关珊楠的问题
I wanted to ask you some questions about Shannan,
如果可以的话
if that's okay.
有没有任何你知道的
Is there anything that you can tell me
关于珊楠生活中出现的男性的信息
about the men in Shannan's life?
她有个男朋友  亚历克斯·迪亚兹
She has a boyfriend, Alex Diaz.
还有其他我们应该注意的人吗
Anybody else we should be looking at?
有个司机  白  迈克尔·白
A driver. Pak. Michael Pak.
那个医生是怎么回事
What about the doctor?
什么医生
What doctor?
他给我打过电话
He called me the morning
在珊楠失踪后的那个早上
after she went missing.
他说他见过珊楠并帮了她
He said he saw her and he helped her.
他运营着一个帮助叛逆女孩的救助之家
He runs a home for wayward girls.
还有她的夹克呢
What about her jacket?
我们找到那件夹克并送去检验了
We have the jacket and it's being tested.
你能想起来那个医生的名字吗
Can you recall this doctor's name?
操
Fuck. Oh.
哈珀  哈斯克尔
Harper? Haskell?
-没关系  没关系的  -我记不清了
- It's okay. It's okay. It's okay. - I don't remember.
吉尔伯特夫人
Mrs. Gilbert,
目前我们所知的信息非常有限
there's a lot we don't know at the moment.
所以非常重要的一点是
Which is why it's really important
你不能透露给媒体任何本案的信息
that you don't talk to the media.
让我们来进行调查
Let us handle that.
一个不慎之词  媒体就会大做文章
One wrong word, and they'll make a meal out of it.
为了你好
It's in your best interest.
也是为了莎伦
Sharon's, too.
是"珊楠"
It's "Shannan"
位于纽约长岛的美丽沙滩
The beautiful beaches of Long Island, New York
已变成最近一起凶杀疑案的背景地
have become the latest backdrop in a murder mystery.
受害者们从事着高风险行业
The victims were engaged in a high-risk business,
而这些凶杀案看起来
and these homicides appear to us
和他们所从事的行业有着直接联系
to be directly related to that business.
经法医鉴证四名女子
The Medical Examiner determined the cause of death
是被勒致死的
for the four women to be strangulation.
每具尸体都被特意放置在
Each body meticulously placed in bur--
24岁的珊楠·吉尔伯特
24-year-old Shannan Gilbert,
一名来自新泽西的妓女
a prostitute from Jersey-
我希望他们不要称她为妓女
I wish they wouldn't call her a prostitute.
那你期望他们叫她什么  律师吗
Well, what do you expect them to call her, a lawyer?
我总是跟你们说  姑娘们
I always told you, girls,
有因必有果
the choices you make eventually catch up with you.
你从没说过这句话
You've never said that.
听起来  你像是在责怪她
It sounds like you're blaming her.
或许我应该怪你
Maybe I should blame you
你没有告诉我
for not telling me
珊楠有一段受虐的恋爱关系
she's in an abusive relationship.
就像你没有告诉我她是在做妓女一样吗
Like you not telling me she was a prostitute?
为什么你不阻止她
Why didn't you do anything?
还有什么你没告诉我
What else aren't you telling me?
我像往常一样在车里等着
I was waiting in the car like usual.
一边在和朋友玩填词游戏
Uh, playing Words with Friends.
然后当约翰
And that's when the John...
这个肥仔到车窗边说
this fat fuck comes up to the window and he says...
你得把她从我家弄走
You gotta get her out of my house.
开他妈玩笑呢
Fucking kidding me?
于是我进到里面
So, I went inside and...
珊楠在沙发后面蜷缩着  在发抖
Shannan was behind the couch on her hands and knees, shaking.
-然后她打了911  -救救我
- And she called 911. - Help me!
她开始喊叫
She started screaming.
你在干嘛  珊楠  停下来
What are you doing? Shannan! Stop!
救命  有人吗
Help! Somebody!
珊楠
Shannan!
接着我冲她喊"我在试图帮你"
So then I said, "I'm trying to help you."
最后  我说了句"操蛋"
Finally, I said "Fuck it,"
你懂的
you know,
然后我一个人 开到橡树海滩  去敲门
and just drove to Oak Beach to knock on doors myself.
我和约翰聊了聊
I talked to the John. Um...
对了  我遇着一个愿意提供帮助的
Oh, I met this guy with a limp
跛着脚的男人
who was actually willing to help.
约翰的姓是什么
What was the name of the John?
布鲁尔
Brewer.
他一定是做了什么吓到了珊楠
He must've done something to spook her.
萨福克县警察局正在对
Suffolk County Police are questioning
一名与珊楠·吉尔伯特失踪有关的
an Oak Beach resident
橡树海滩的居民进行询问
in connection with the disappearance of Shannan Gilbert
并确认了海洋公园路边的四具骸骨是
and have identified the four skeletons along Ocean Parkway
莫琳·贝纳德·巴恩斯  梅利莎·巴泰勒米
as Maureen Bainard-Barnes, Melissa Barthelemy,
安珀·科斯特洛和梅根·沃特曼
Amber Costello, and Megan Waterman.
她们都是在克雷格信息网上发广告
All sex workers advertising on Craigslist
从2007年到最近3个月前
who have been missing since as far back as 2007
失踪的性工作者  局长
and as recently as three months ago. Commissioner--
为什么我们是从这些
Why are we learning about this
该死的今日新闻中了解到这些信息
on the goddamned Today show?
你觉得怎么样
What do you think?
为珊楠·玛丽亚·吉尔伯特祈祷
那些女孩都有这种
All the other girls have one.
那些女孩都死了
All the other girls are dead.
她们的家人邀请我们去守夜
Their families invited us to a vigil.
-你和他们聊天了  -线上聊的
- You've been talking to them? - Online.
我们不会去守夜的
Oh, we're not going to any vigil.
-为什么不呢  -因为珊楠根本没死
- Why not? - Because Shannan's not dead.
萨福克县警察局
Suffolk County Police.
我想和多默局长谈谈
I'd like to speak to Commissioner Dormer.
你告诉他我是玛丽·吉尔伯特
Okay, you tell him this is Mari Gilbert calling,
如果他没有在一小时内回我电话
and if I don't hear back within the hour,
我就把车开进他家的草坪
I'm gonna drive my car into his front fucking lawn.
晚饭的时候我会回来
Okay, I'll see you at dinner.
橡树海滩住户  约瑟夫·布鲁尔
Oak Beach resident, Joseph Brewer,
是珊楠·吉尔伯特的雇主
who hired Shannan Gilbert,
在通过测谎仪测试之后
has been cleared by Suffolk County Police
已经被萨福克县警察局判为无罪
after taking a polygraph,
但仍有两个问题没有解决
leaving two questions still unanswered:
谁在长岛杀了性工作者
who is killing sex workers on Long Island,
以及珊楠·吉尔伯特在哪里
and where is Shannan Gilbert?
警察确认了四位女性
Police have identified the remains
-的尸体身份  -是我  你好
- of the four women... - Yes, hello.
这是我打给你们第二十次了
It's the 20th goddamned time I've called!
他们做了什么搜查工作
What are they doing to find her,
为什么他们把那个贱人放了
and why did they let that fuck go?
-他雇佣了  -珊楠·吉尔伯特
- He hire... -Shannan Gilbert
一个妓女在克雷格信息网上
a prostitute who went missing
克雷格信息网  大型免费分类广告网站
约见了一位顾客之后失踪
after apparently meeting a client on Craigslist.
还有数十名女性  被谋杀后
Are dozens more murdered women dumped like trash
像垃圾一样被丢弃在同一海滩上
on the same strip of beach,
等待着被发现吗
waiting to be uncovered?
我们生活的海滩变成了墓地
We are live at the beach-turned-burial-ground.
这些女孩们很容易接触  并且很弱势
The girls are very available. They're very vulnerable.
她们没有家庭
They have no family,
也没有人在寻找她们
and there's nobody out there looking for them.
怎么了  吉尔伯特小姐
What's going on, Mrs. Gilbert?
要么是你的电话坏了
Either your phone's broke
要么你的秘书是个白痴
or your secretary's a moron
因为我至少给你留了50条消息
because I must have left 50 messages for you.
这是我的女儿  珊楠·玛丽亚·吉尔伯特
This is my daughter, Shannan Maria Gilbert.
她失踪一天
There's one here for every day that she's missing.
我就在这贴一天寻人启事
and I'm gonna continue posting these.
直到你们找到她  或被这些纸烦死
until you either find her or die of paper cuts.
不要忽视我
Do not ignore me.
没有人忽视你  吉尔伯特小姐
Nobody is ignoring you, Mrs. Gilbert.
我一向很记仇  如果你不帮我的话
I have a talent for holding grudges and unless you help me,
我一定会想办法搞砸你
I'm gonna raise more hell than you can handle.
还有  你他妈再敢叫我女儿妓女试试
And don't you ever fucking call my daughter a prostitute again!
告诉他们我们会守夜的
Okay, tell them we'll do the vigil,
但我们想要先见见他们
but we want to meet them first.
确保每个人都会来
And make sure everybody comes.
你怎么穿成这样
What are you wearing?
为珊楠·玛丽亚·吉尔伯特祈祷
聊天记录
好消息  我们要来了
待在旅馆一直到周六的守夜  明天在餐厅见吧
我们会跟你们一起守夜\n会在旅馆里待到周六
这里距离橡树海滩很远
It's a long way to Oak Beach.
你们在路上聊了什么呢
What were you guys talking about?
我不记得了  我......
I don't know. I...
聊了工作
work.
天气
The weather...
她和她的男朋友在哈德逊商城
Her and her boyfriend sneaking Taco Bell
放弗雷迪的新电影的时候偷墨西哥卷去了
in the new Freddy movie over at the Hudson Mall.
她有提到她要去看她妈妈吗
Did she say anything about going to visit her mom?
等等  你是认真的吗
Wait. Are you serious?
你了解她妈妈吗
Do you know anything about her mom?
天哪  这些女人真是可怜
Oh, my God. These women are so pathetic.
我们说的越少越好
The less we say, the better.
我们不需要让她们知道我们的私事
We don't need them knowing our personal business.
这是用来干嘛的
What's that for?
这是我的笔记本  我要做笔记
My notebook. I'm gonna take notes.
或许我们该都来介绍一下自己
Maybe we should go around?
我是米西
I'm Missy.
我为莫琳来的  从康涅狄格州开车
I drove in from Connecticut for my sister, Maureen.
很高兴能我能亲自见到你们
It's so good to finally meet all of you in person.
妈
Mom.
说些什么
Say something.
我是洛兰
Uh, Lorraine.
我的女儿是梅根
My daughter's Megan.
我从缅因州来的  我为了过来卖掉了电视
I sold my TV to be here from Maine,
这样我才有钱待在这里直到守夜结束
so I have the cash to stay here until the vigil.
我是林恩
I'm Lynn.
我的女儿是梅利莎
My daughter is Melissa.
这是我的另一个女儿  阿曼达
This is my other daughter, Amanda.
我们来自布法罗
We came here from Buffalo.
金来了
Oh. Kim is here.
抱歉  我来晚了
Sorry, I'm late, y'all.
我们正在轮流介绍自己
We were just going around introducing ourselves.
我们从哪来  我们为谁来的
Where we're from, who we've lost.
好吧  我是金
Okay. Kim...
我来自北卡罗来纳州
North Carolina. Um...
我喜欢石板路冰淇淋
I like Rocky Road ice cream
也喜欢在海滩上散步
and long walks on the beach,
我的妹妹是安珀
and my sister was Amber.
我少说了什么吗
Did I miss anything?
等等  你是认真的吗
Wait. Are you serious?
你了解她妈妈吗
Do you know anything about her mom?
那女人可行了
'Cause she's a real piece of work.
她在她女儿小时候抛弃了她
Yeah, abandoned her own daughter when she was just a kid.
珊楠一辈子都在寄养家庭里
Shannan was in and out of foster homes her whole life.
她妈妈就只会拿她的钱
All her mom is good for is taking her money.
根本不关心珊楠的钱是怎么赚来的
Doesn't even care how Shannan made it.
只要她能分到钱
Just as long as she shared the wealth.
我的女儿有3部手机
My daughter had three cellphones.
她在克雷格信息网工作
She was working on the... Craigslist.
莫琳也是这样
Yes, so did Maureen.
梅利莎也是
So did Melissa.
她们都这样  所以她们的结局也都一样
They all did. That's why they're all so the same,
因为在网上  你什么都能买到
because online, you can practically go shopping.
他们迟早会抓住这个人的
Sooner or later, they're gonna get this guy.
他们可以
There's gotta be some...
追踪电脑
computer trace they can do.
不是  他们不是用邮件联系的
Mm-mm. They don't get you on email.
是你要把自己的号码放网上  他们会打
You post a number, then they call.
而且还是很难追踪的
Which is untraceable
因为女孩们都是用一次性电话的
because the girls work on burner phones.
你懂不少啊
Look at you, knowing your shit.
他们认为女孩们都是瘾君子
They think they're all drug addicts.
梅利莎从来没碰过毒品
Melissa wasn't even into drugs.
莫琳也没有
Neither was Maureen.
她只是喝酒
She drank.
喝酒总比毒品好  因为喝酒合法
Drinking's better than drugs because it's legal.
但是可卡因才能让生意做下去
But coke is the best way to keep a call going.
能真的赚到钱
Make some real bank.
爱信不信  你们的女孩子都懂
Your girls knew that, whether you want to believe it or not.
他们告诉我梅根去她想去的地方了
They told me Megan was where she wants to be.
还有
That, uh...
她不爱我
That she didn't love me.
虽然很伤心  但我感到了一点解脱
As sad as it is, I feel some kind of relief.
至少警察终于关注了
At least they're finally paying attention.
你在开玩笑吗
Are you shitting me?
如果你觉得他们在
If you think they give one goddamn
关注这些女孩吗  你就是在妄想
about these girls, you're delusional.
他们都没在寻找女孩们
They weren't searching for them.
警察就是停在路边
A cop stopped along the side of the road
让他的狗去拉屎的时候
to let his dog take a shit.
意外地发现她们的
He accidentally found them.
我的意思就是
What I meant was...
至少这件事被报道了  人们都知道了
at least it's on the news and people are aware of it.
你看过这些新闻吗
Have you watched the news?
都是在说  "他是个警察"  "他是抓捕者"
It's all, "He's a cop," "He's a clammer,"
他是这  他是那
he's this, he's that.
全都是  "他"  "他"  "他"
It's all "him," "him," "him."
那我们的女孩呢  谁在谈论她们
What about our girls? Who's talking about them?
当他们谈论到女孩们时
And when they do,
都是在说  "妓女"  "卖淫者"
it's "prostitute," "hooker,"
"性工作者"  "性伴侣"
"sex worker," "escort."
从来不是  "朋友"  "姐妹"
Never "friend," "sister,"
"母亲"  "女儿"
"mother," "daughter."
他们根本不关心
They don't care.
他们都在责怪女孩们
They blame them.
作为母亲
And it's our job, as mothers,
作为姐妹  我们要做的就是
and sisters,
确保这些女孩们不被遗忘
to make sure these girls are not forgotten.
我们应该继续等守夜吗
So, should we wait on the vigil?
不  我们要去守夜  我们要去橡树海滩
No, we're doing the vigil. We're going to Oak Beach,
去他们的前院
to their front fucking yard.
谁叫了媒体
Who tipped them off?
这是一个私人社区  我会叫警察的
This is a private community! I'll call the police!
叫吧  他们要花一个小时才过得来
Go ahead. It'll take them an hour to get here.
说到这个  我可以借一下你手机吗
Speaking of which, can I borrow your phone?
好啊  为什么
Sure. Why?
他们已经知道我的号码了
They already know my number.
这里有个疯女人要糟践橡树海滩
There's a crazy lady about to tear through Oak Beach.
快点来
Come quick.
谁住在这
Who lives here?
那个雇佣我女儿的贱人
The son of a bitch who hired her.
妈
Mom?
Mom.
十二分钟
Twelve minutes.
现在我们都知道  你可以及时出现
Now we both know you can show up on time
还有你的秘书不是个白痴
and your secretary's not a retard.
我们可以回我办公室谈吗
Can we just go back to my office and talk about this?
我们就在这谈
We'll talk right here.
这是一个
This is a...
这是一个私人社区
This is a private community.
那你为什么不逮捕我
Well, then why don't you arrest me?
听好了  我来这儿是帮你的
Listen, I came here to do you a favor.
我不想看到你戴着手铐被拖走
I don't want to see you hauled away in handcuffs.
你不明白当那些穿制服的警察来到这
Don't you understand that when the uniforms get here,
你就会因非法侵入而被定罪
they're gonna cite you for trespassing.
好吧  我直话直说
Okay, let me get this straight.
我女儿打电话求救
My daughter calls for help
可你们花了一个小时才到这
but it takes you an hour to get here,
但是戴普夫特·外福斯打电话给你们
but the Stepford Wives call you
你们出现得比做三明治还快
and you show up in less time than it takes to make a sandwich!
不管你是在找什么
Whatever it is that you're looking for,
吉尔伯特小姐  都不在这
Mrs. Gilbert, it is not here.
那为什么我14岁的孩子刚刚
Okay, then why did my 14-year-old
在你们放走的那个男人的家前
just find her sister's earring
找到了她姐姐的耳环
outside the home of the man that you just set free?
珊楠在早上4点51分时尖叫地穿过这里
Shannan went screaming through here at 4:51 in the morning,
但没有人帮她
and no one helped her.
有人感到愤怒吗  有人表示担心吗
Where is the outrage? Where's the concern?
要是有四具尸体出现在我家附近
Four dead bodies show up in my neighborhood,
我早就在屋顶上吼起来了  到底发生了啥
I'd be shouting from the rooftops to get to the bottom of it.
他们在隐瞒什么
What are they hiding?
你在隐瞒什么  吉尔伯特小姐
What are you hiding, Mrs. Gilbert?
你从来没告诉我珊楠是在寄养家庭长大的
You never told me that Shannan grew up in foster care.
你也从来没告诉过我
You never told me that you nearly got shit-canned
你差点因为部门管理不善而被解雇
for mismanaging your department.
继续努力吧  长官
Keep up the good work, Commissioner.
操
Fuck's sake.
我把所有我看到的门牌号都写下来了
I wrote down every house number and license plate I saw.
我们需要和这些人  还有这些人谈一谈
We need to talk to these people and these people.
他们有可能看到过她
They might've seen her.
没人会说的  他们只希望我们走远点
No one's gonna talk 'cause they want us out.
这些人都是一伙的
These guys are looking out for each other.
他们都有朋友在萨福克县警察局
They all have friends in Suffolk PD.
警察说每个人都通过了测谎仪测试
The police said everybody passed lie detector tests.
对  但是每个人都可以通过测谎仪测试
Yeah, but anybody can pass a lie detector test
只要他们问你  "你叫什么名字
if all they ask you is "What's your name,
还有你喜欢的颜色"
and your favorite color."
这听上去好像是珊楠在逃离她的司机
It sounds like Shannan's running from her driver.
你可以在911通话记录里听到他的声音
You can hear him in the 911 call.
这没道理
That makes no sense.
不管情况多糟糕  我都会去找我的司机
I don't care how fucked up I am, my ass is going to that driver
因为他是我唯一的出路
because he's my way out.
司机是安全保障  这也是雇他的原因
He's my safety. That's what you pay him for.
也许他生气了  因为她没付钱给他
Well, maybe he was mad she didn't pay him.
为什么突然间变成了她没付钱给司机
Why would she all of a sudden not pay her driver?
也许因为方式她需要给家里些钱
Maybe because she was bringing money home.
所以你并不知道她付没付钱
Okay, do you don't know she didn't pay him.
你只是在猜罢了
You're just guessing.
这只是假设
Well, I'm assuming.
她也可能被迫吸毒  喝醉了或嗑上头了
She's probably forced to get stoned, drunk, high--
-没有强迫这一说  -好吧随便了
- Not forced. - Okay, whatever.
我只是说  我也经过那样的生活
I'm just saying, I've lived it.
我也只是说  你不是珊楠
Well, I'm just saying, you're not Shannan.
玛丽  我可怜你
Mari, I feel for you...
比可怜我自己
more than I feel for myself
或在场其他人更甚
or any of the other ladies here,
因为珊楠仍然毫无音讯
because Shannan's still missing.
知道了总比一无所知要好
And knowing is better than not knowing.
但是你不会真的觉得
But you don't really think that...
我是说  或许接受这件事不会有其他转机
I'm just saying it might be good to accept
对你也许会更好
that there isn't another ending to all this.
你他妈的知道这么多  是什么狗结局啊
What's that ending, if you know so goddamned much?
未知来电
你好
Hello?
是玛丽·吉尔伯特吗
Is this Mari Gilbert?
是的
Yes.
我是乔·斯卡利斯
My name's Joe Scalise.
有些事情  你可能感兴趣
I have some information you're gonna want to hear.
我是乔·布鲁尔的邻居  约翰
I'm a neighbor of Joe Brewer, the john.
我从你发布的传单里  找到了你的号码
I got your number from one of those fliers you posted.
萨福克县警局没有回我电话
Suffolk PD don't return my calls no more.
你要知道的是  在橡树海滩
You're gonna learn that the good people of Oak Beach,
善良的人也许只学会了一件事
if they live by one thing, it's this:
就是对那些可能
be wary of those who would...
可能会破坏美好事物的人保持警惕
who would ruin a very good thing.
夫人  他们最害怕的
You are, madam,
就是像您这样穷追不舍的人
the wayfarer they've been dreading.
我不知道珊楠是个妓女
I didn't know Shannan was a prostitute.
我也不知道她有往家里寄钱
I didn't know she was bringing home money.
她从没让任何人帮她
She doesn't let anyone help her.
我还以为我们一直是一起的
I thought we were doing this together.
太恼人了
So fucking annoying.
抱歉
Sorry.
我们不是在跟踪你们
We weren't following you.
有点算吧
We kind of were.
你俩在聊什么
What are you two talking about?
家庭
Families.
是啊
Yeah.
跟我说说珊楠的优点吧
Tell me something nice about Shannan.
她提前两年从高中毕业
She graduated high school two years early.
她非常聪明
She was smart.
而且她是我们家第一个大学生
And she was the first one in our family to go to college.
我叫她  "歌姬"
I called her "Diva."
因为她就是我眼中的歌者
Because she's such a little diva.
安珀身高一米五
Amber stood 4'11"
连90斤都没有
and weighed 100 pounds soaking wet.
她的腿看起来和小鸡腿一样
Her legs looked like little chicken drumsticks.
她失踪那天我还跟她说话了
I spoke to her the day she went missing.
我们当时在吵架
We were in a fight.
你现在走的地方
You're walking through
是凶手抛尸的地方
what used to be the killer's dumping ground.
他只会把尸体搬到路边上
He only moved the bodies to the road
因为这一片区域被划成
because this whole area is set to be
"蚊子计划"的范围
drained as part of the mosquito project.
意思是人们在闲逛时
That means people poking around,
总会发现不该看见的东西
seeing things they shouldn't.
在这
Here.
看
Look.
这是他储存物资的地方
This is where he keeps his supplies.
那  在哪呢
But... where?
快进去  快
Go, go, go.
-这种事经常发生  -怎么了
- Shit like that happens. - What's up?
天哪
Oh, God.
冷静  别
Easy. Just...
乔·布鲁尔没有杀害珊楠
Joe Brewer didn't kill Shannan.
他可能是个反社会者
He may be a sociopath,
但他不是精神病患者
but he's not the psychopath.
这应该归罪于  皮特·哈克特
That honor goes to Peter Hackett.
哈克特医生
Dr. Hackett?
听着  我知道你和你的下属并不在意
Look, I know you and your buddies don't give a shit.
别担心  你不用忍受我多久了
Don't worry. You're not gonna have to put up with me much longer.
但是现在  这还是我的案子
But for the moment, this is my case.
懂了吗
Okay?
-我需要一个犯人  一个名字  -没问题
- I want a suspect. I want a name. - Okay.
皮特·哈克特  皮特·哈克特医生
Peter Hackett. Dr. Peter Hackett.
他住在橡树海滩
He lives in Oak Beach.
很高兴再见到你  吉尔伯特女士
It's nice to see you again, Ms. Gilbert.
我在他家附近的棚子里看到一堆粗麻布
I saw spools of burlap in a shed by his house.
得了吧  你在说什么呢
Come on. What are you talking about?
任何一个捡牡蛎的  承包商  园艺师
Every clammer, contractor, landscaper
房子附近都有粗麻布  算了吧
has got burlap by his house. Come on.
但是医生呢
But a doctor?
我就这么说吧  不如让
I tell you what, why don't you let
警察来做警察该做的事呢  亲爱的
the policemen do the police work, honey?
-你为什么不吸我的老二  -真优雅
- Why don't you suck my dick? - Classy.
这个人在她失踪第二天早上
This is the guy who called me
打过电话给我
the morning after she disappeared.
他说他帮助过她
He said that he helped her.
拜托  你会把它记录下来吗
Come on. Aren't you gonna write it down?
你他妈是在逗我吗
Are you fucking kidding me? Hmm?
记下来
Write it down.
什么
What?
我说把它记下来
I said write it down.
我在谷歌上查了莎拉吃的药
I googled Sarra's medication.
所以我知道那是一种镇定剂
So I know it's a mood stabilizer.
她告诉我你带她去看心理医生了
She told me you took her to a psychiatrist.
你为什么不告诉我
Why didn't you tell me?
没什么好说的
There's nothing to tell.
需要六周药物才能见效
It takes six weeks for the medication to have any effect,
到时候我们才能知道有没有用
so we'll know more then.
要么友好
要么离开
你好  有什么需要帮忙的吗
Hello. Can I help you?
皮特·哈克特是一个非常好的邻居
Peter Hackett's the best neighbor you can have.
一旦谁有麻烦  他总是第一个打电话来
Ever there's a problem, he's always the first one to call.
你还记得那天晚上发生了什么吗
Do you remember anything from that night?
我记得那个女孩被下了很多药
Yeah, that girl was pretty well drugged up.
-什么  -她几乎都站不起来了
- What? - She couldn't hardly stand.
-什么  -我和她说话的时候
- Excuse me? - She almost fell down twice
-她几乎摔倒了两次  -等等  你见过她吗
- when I was talking to her. - Wait, you saw her?
-你为什么不报警  -我报了
- Why didn't you call the police? - I did.
-她当时说了什么  -她说了一通胡话
- What was she saying? - It wasn't making sense.
"帮我  帮帮我  他们想杀我"
"Help me. Help me. They're going to kill me."
于是我让她坐在门廊上
So I sat her down on the porch,
然后我说  "放松点"
and I said, "Relax."
我告诉她我已经报警了
I told her that I called the police
而且他们已经在来的路上了
and they were on their way.
我刚说完  她就跑了
As soon as I said that, she ran.
总之
Anyhow...
-怎么了  -她从楼梯上摔了下来  然后
- What? - ...she fell down the stairs and...
就往那边跑了
she ran that way.
等等  那些监控摄像头能用吗
Wait, do those security cameras work?
橡树海滩联系中心
这里是放监控录像的地方吗
Is this where they keep the security footage?
你是新闻报社的人吗
Are you from the news?
很遗憾  从那天晚上起就没有了
We, unfortunately, don't have it from that night.
它会自动覆盖历史记录  这是循环运行的
It gets taped over automatically. It runs on a loop.
非常抱歉
I'm sorry.
但是警察那有备份  是吗
But the police got a copy, right?
他们没问过  我们也很奇怪
We found it odd they never asked.
抱歉  你是谁呢
I'm sorry, who are you?
你为什么不交给他们
Why didn't you give it to them?
为什么我丈夫还没来呢
Why don't I get my husband?
他才是负责人
He oversees all that.
我只是来给他送午餐的
I just came by to drop off his lunch.
橡树岛警察游行
萨福克县警察局慈善协会
我能帮你什么吗  我是皮特·哈克特医生
How can I help you? Dr. Peter Hackett.
我妻子告诉我你是一名记者
My wife tells me you're a reporter.
我在这住了三十年了
I've lived here for 30 years.
橡树海滩没有什么我不知道的
There's not a thing I don't know about Oak Beach.
这就像一个微型政府  而我是主导者
We're like a miniature government here, and I pound the gavel.
芭芭拉  给我们来点咖啡吧
Barbara, why don't you put on some coffee?
已经有了  亲爱的
It's on, dear.
那为什么不煮点新鲜的呢
Then why don't you refresh it?
我在新闻里见过你
I, uh... recognize you from the news.
为你感到遗憾
I'm so sorry.
到底发生了什么
What happened?
这可是个价值64000美元的问题
Well, that's the $64,000 question.
但是你打电话给我了
But you called me.
你说什么
I beg your pardon?
报告航标10.46  海洋公园路
Unit report to mile marker 10.46, Ocean Parkway
可能有尸体残骸
for possible remains sighting.
刚刚抵达  准备去看看  你们原地待命
Just arriving. Going to check it out. Stand by.
我们在雪松海滩附近的
We got a 10-54 on Ocean Parkway
海洋公园路发现了一具尸体
near Cedar Beach.
操
Fuck.
珊楠最后出现
Last place Shannan was seen was in clear view
在摄像机拍摄到的清晰画面里
of a video camera,
而且哈克特掌握了录像
and Hackett's in charge of the footage!
好的  我会深入查查的
Okay. I'll look into it.
他已经删掉了
He erased it.
什么  你发现了些什么线索吗
What? Did you find something?
吉尔伯特女士  你真的不应该来这里
Mrs. Gilbert, you really shouldn't be here.
-你能带她去马路边上吗  -你找到了什么
- Can you take her to the road? - What did you find?
放开我
Let go of me.
包里面是什么
What's in the bag?
这个和其他四个不一样
This one's not like the other four.
其他都是在一英里外的灌木丛里发现的
Those were in the bramble a mile away.
这一块上面没有粗麻布  而且没有舌骨
There's no burlap on this one, either, or hyoid bones.
颚板找到了吗
Any indication of a jaw plate?
没有  长官
No, sir.
好  我们走吧
Right. Let's go.
今天24名警察扩大了搜寻尸体的范围
Two dozen police recruits expanded the search for bodies today
从灌木丛扩大到了海滩
from the thicket to the beach.
萨福克县警察局也扩大了搜索范围
Suffolk County Police also expanded the total search area.
这一组新招募的警员
This platoon of recruits conducted
在雪松海滩开展了网络排查
a grid-pattern search on Cedar Beach.
那在吉尔戈和橡树海滩之间
It's between Gilgo and Oak Beach,
也是先前发现尸体的地方
where the previous bodies were found.
自去年以来  搜寻工作一直受限于
Since last year, the search has been hampered
丛林的恶劣条件
by the harsh conditions in the thicket.
又硬又结实的维吉尼亚灌木丛
Hard, wiry brush called Virginia Weepers
随处可见
and Bittersweet so thick,
你无法看到十英尺外的任何物体
you cannot see a person or dog just ten feet away.
皮特·哈克特医生
Dr. Peter Hackett.
金又重操旧业了
Kim's working again.
"卡罗琳娜"  是她的艺名
"Carolina" is her street name.
她一小时前发布了这个
She posted this an hour ago.
天哪  金
Oh, Kim.
她在想什么呢
What is she thinking?
我平时很忙
I'm a busy guy.
我每天拨打接听很多电话
I make and take a lot of calls.
但怎么会打给一个我不认识的女人呢
But how would I call a woman I don't even know?
我是一个医生
I'm a doctor...
不是魔术师
not a magician.
她说
She said that...
是你告诉她  你帮助了他女儿
that you told her that you helped her daughter.
我希望她不会
I hope she doesn't blame herself
因为她女儿的事而自责
for the life her daughter led.
但是
But...
有其母必有其女
apples don't fall far from the tree.
我说的对吗
Am I right?
所以  关于那晚你还记得些什么
So, what do you remember from that night?
我想那是  我和芭芭拉在佛罗里达的时候
I think that's when Barbara and I were in Florida.
你钓过马林鱼吗
You ever been marlin fishing?
但是那时候你在这里
But you were here.
因为当他女儿的男友
Because when the daughter's boyfriend
第二天过来找她
came the next morning to look for her,
难道你没有帮忙找她吗
didn't you offer to help search for her?
佛罗里达可能是
Florida might have been...
一周前的事了  哦  好吧
the week before. Oh, okay.
是的  我看到这个孩子在附近转来转去
That's right. I saw this kid tooling around,
他给我讲了他的故事  我无法拒绝他
and he told me his story and I couldn't turn him away.
我们这里都这么做  我们帮助大家
That's what we do around here, we help people.
如我直言  哈克特医生
With all due respect, Dr. Hackett,
你住在一个封闭的小区里
you're living in a gated community
小区有一块牌子  上面写着:
with a sign that says:
"要么友好  要么离开"
"Be nice or leave."
我不知道这是否传达了特定的信息
I don't know that that sends that particular message.
听着  警察已经来过了
Look... the police came.
他们说一切正常
They said everything was kosher.
是的
Right.
但是
But...
你为什么不给他们看监控录像
why didn't you show them the security footage?
为什么他们没有要求提供监控录像
Why didn't they ask for it?
这不是我的调查  独行侠
This is not my investigation, kemosabe.
你是头儿
You're the head honcho.
也许你应该好好教育你的手下
Maybe you ought to teach your cops better.
一个女孩儿失踪了
A girl goes missing
然而你有一卷监控录像
and you have a tape.
你是说你看都没看过吗
Are you telling me that you didn't at least watch it?
那可是诱导取证
That would be tampering with evidence.
我说的对吗
Am I right?
橡树岛海滩协会的私人财产
禁止非法侵入
皮特·哈克特是一个自负的吹牛大王
Peter Hackett is a self-important blowhard.
他没有带头指控  这个行为本身
The very fact that he's not leading the charge in this
就是你需要关注的关键证据
is all the evidence you need to point a finger.
好的  如果这是真的
Okay, if that's true,
为什么珊楠没有和其他女孩在一起
why wasn't Shannan found with the other girls?
因为  袭击她是计划之外的事
'Cause the attack on her didn't go as planned.
她逃出来了
She'd gone off running.
有人见过她  警察来了
People had seen her. The police came.
这太冒险了
It just became too risky.
他声称  他为叛逆女孩营造了一个家
He tells people that he runs a home for wayward girls.
他帮她们戒毒  他拯救了她们
That he rehabs them. That he saves them.
他真正的意思是埋葬她们
What he really means is he buries them.
他的客厅里有一张检查台
He's got an examination table in his living room.
他所谓的"叛逆女孩之家"
And his "home for wayward girls"
其实是"墓地"的代号
is really just code for "graveyard."
那么珊楠在哪呢
Then where is Shannan?
在他的后院
In his backyard.
那片沼泽
The marsh.
那是唯一还没有被搜查的地方
It's the one place they haven't searched.
我们发现了另一个女孩
We found another one.
尸体碎块  被肢解了
Pieces, dismembered.
取证科说匹配上了一双腿
Forensics says it matches a pair of severed legs
在96年的一个装着些腿的塑料袋里
found in a plastic bag in '96.
-1996年吗  -是的
- '96? - Yeah, '96.
你是说有人在海洋公园
Are you telling me that somebody's been dumping bodies
持续抛尸了他妈15年吗
in Ocean Parkway for 15 fucking years?
看起来像是这样的
It looks like it.
这是什么
Hey, what is this?
珊楠·吉尔伯特的医疗记录
Shannan Gilbert's medical records?
不是吧  你认真的吗
Come on, seriously?
你真的以为  你可以
You really think you're gonna find
从这些医疗记录里找到答案吗
any answers in these medical records?
听着  如果她还活着
Look, if she was still around,
我们现在已经找到她了
we would have found her by now.
我的意思是  实话实说
I mean, honestly,
谁会花这么多时间找一个失踪的妓女
who spends this much time looking for a missing hooker?
如果你是来给我说教的  省省吧
If you're here to give me some big speech, save it.
我已经听别人那听过了
I already heard it from the others.
金  我知道你很坚强
Kim, I know you're strong,
你以为你能应付任何事情  但是
and you think you can handle whatever comes your way, but...
这太愚蠢了
this is just plain stupid.
每个人都有自己的命运
Everyone has their destiny.
也许安珀的是安珀的  也许这是我的
Maybe Amber's was Amber's, and maybe this is mine.
你不是真心相信的
You don't really believe that.
你这么做  是因为内心深处
You're only doing this because deep down,
你认为你就值这么多
you think that's all you're worth,
但是这不是真的
but that's not true.
你给珊楠说这个了吗
You tell that to Shannan?
是我把安珀扯进来的  你知道吗
I got Amber into this, you know?
你尝试过了  玛丽
You tried, Mari.
-给你  -谢谢
- Here. - Thank you.
林恩的男朋友认识个做衣服的人
Lynn's boyfriend knew a guy.
我们都穿着它们去守夜
We're all wearing them to the vigil.
-打开电视  -为什么
- Turn on the TV. - Why?
也没有证据表明
...there's also no evidence to suggest
这是同一个杀手干的
that it's the work of a single killer.
虽然  珊楠·吉尔伯特
Although Shannan GIlbert
恰巧在同一时间同一地点失踪了
coincidentally went missing at the same time in the same place,
但是她不符合受害者的侧写特征
she doesn't fit the victim profile.
她是唯一一个没有单独来橡树海滩的人
She was the only one who didn't come to Oak Beach alone
她还有个司机
because she had a driver.
哦  天呐
Oh, God.
我们将继续寻找她  但是
We will continue to look for her, but...
除非我们找到谋杀的证据
until we find evidence of foul play,
吉尔伯特女士将不再被认为
Miss Gilbert will no longer be considered
与这个案子相关
a part of this larger case.
局长
Commissioner...
-暂时就这些  -操
- That's all for the moment. - Fuck!
是的  我是玛丽·吉尔伯特
Yeah, this is Mari Gilbert...
你还好吗
Hey, you okay?
他们停止寻找珊楠了
They stopped looking for Shannan.
他们不再找她了
They're not looking for her anymore.
-没事  -我们要做什么
- It's okay. - What are we gonna do?
为什么他们
Why did they...
所以我们来这了
That's why we're here.
好吗
Okay?
是的  你说的对
Yeah, right.
没事的
You're okay.
我一会儿就回来
I'll just be a minute.
你怎么能说珊楠跟这起案子没有联系
How can you say Shannan's not connected?
她最后一次被看见
She was last seen three miles
在距离那些女孩3英里的地方
from the other girls.
她跟他们一样20多岁
She was in her 20s, just like them.
她跟她们一样年轻
She was small, just like them.
她跟他们一样在克雷格信息网上
She was on Craigslist, just like them.
如果不是因为她
None of those other girls
这些女孩不会被发现
would've been found if it wasn't for her.
这不代表我们将停止寻找她
It doesn't mean that we're gonna stop looking for her.
妈妈  妈妈  哈克特呢
Mom! Mom! What about Hackett?
即使他打电话给你
Even if he did call you, it...
也不是犯罪的证据
it's not evidence of guilt.
他对此撒谎是证据
Lying about it is.
我知道你很生气  吉尔伯特女士  但是
I understand that you're angry, Mrs. Gilbert, but...
警察做事需要证据  不是愤怒
a policeman deals in evidence, not anger.
你在什么幸运饼上看到的
Ha, ha! What fortune cookie did you read that in?
妈妈  快来  他们在等你
Mom, hurry. They're waiting.
给我一分钟
Give me a minute!
你不懂的
You have no idea, you know,
真正要担心的是没有线索
no clue what worry really is.
我们有珊楠的医疗记录
We have Shannan's medical records.
是吗  记录里怎么说
Yeah? What do they say?
我告诉你  什么是上面没说
I'll tell you what they don't say.
记录没有说
They don't say
她以前  怎么把手指塞进喉咙里
how she used to shove her fingers down her throat
然后吐到嘴巴流血的
and puke until her mouth bled.
记录没有说
They don't say
她如何  大半夜的跑到雪地里去的
how she ran out into the snow one night
没穿衣服  冻死个半死
with no clothes on and nearly froze half to death
那时候我为了赚钱
while I was out working graveyards
正在外面上双轮夜班
and doubles just to keep the lights on.
听着  玛丽  我知道你把她送去寄养了
Yeah. Look, Mari, I know that you gave her away to foster care,
我知道你认为把她带回家
and I know you think it's your
是你的责任
responsibility to bring her home again.
但是这不是你的责任
But this isn't on you.
我是她的妈妈
I'm her mother.
都是因为我
It's all on me.
你把她送走的
You gave her away?
看在上帝的份上  舍尔
Oh, for fuck's sake, Sherre,
我们能不能现在不讨论这个
can we not do this right now?
你骗了我
You lied to me.
我没有骗你
I didn't lie.
你告诉我是政府带走她的
You told me the state took her.
那我该说什么
What was I supposed to say?
"妈妈把你姐姐送走了
"Mommy gave your sister away
因为她得不到她需要的帮助"
because she couldn't get her the help she needed."
你觉得我想让珊楠那样吗
Do you think I wanted that for Shannan?
你认为我没有
Do you think I didn't try to do everything in my power
尽我所能帮助她吗
to get her the help she needed?
珊楠有躁郁症
Shannan was bipolar.
她一团糟
She was a mess.
我带她去看我负担不起的医生
I took her to doctors I couldn't afford
给她吃她不愿吃的药
who gave her drugs that she wouldn't take
那药有副作用  我都不忍心看
that had side-effects that I couldn't stand to watch.
我当时也只是个孩子
I was just a kid.
她需要的是爱
What she needed was love.
她一辈子里
It was the only thing she ever wanted her whole...
唯一想要的东西
fucking life.
你又怎么知道她想要什么
Okay, but how do you know what she felt?
因为我也感受到了  妈妈
Because I feel it too, Mom.
珊楠可能走了  但我还在这里
Shannan may be gone but I'm still here.
我还在这里
I'm still here.
哦  我的天呐
Oh, my God.
这些该死的女人  他们给你洗脑了
These fucking women, they've brainwashed you.
你想知道他们为什么这么坚决地要守夜吗
You wanna know why they're so dead set on this vigil?
这是他们否认现实的方法
It's their way of denying
否认自己是糟透了的母亲和姐姐的方式
what god-awful mothers and sisters they were.
他们已经让你觉得
They've convinced you that
我们和他们一样  但我们不是  亲爱的
we are like them, but we are not, honey.
我们一点也不像他们
We are nothing like them.
你说的对
You're right.
对  我们一点也不像她们
No, we're not like them at all.
她们是一家人
They're a family.
我希望她们是我的家人
I wish they were my family.
好吧  也许你的新家庭
Okay. Well, maybe your new family
能支付你的大学学费
will pay for your college
因为我绝对负担不起
because I sure as shit can't afford it.
下一次你要把莎拉送走吗
Are you gonna give away Sarra next?
♪ 天赐恩典 ♪
♪ Amazing grace ♪
♪ 如此甘甜 ♪
♪ How sweet the sound ♪
♪ 我等罪人  竟蒙赦免 ♪
♪ That saved a wretch like me ♪
♪ 昔我迷失 ♪
♪ I once was lost ♪
♪ 今归正途 ♪
♪ But now I'm found ♪
♪ 曾经盲目 ♪
♪ Was blind ♪
♪ 重又得见 ♪
♪ But now I see ♪
你现在要走了吗
You're leaving now?
是的
Yeah.
再见
Goodbye.
照顾好你女儿  好吗
Take care of your girls, okay?
你很幸运  你知道吗
You're lucky, you know?
我是珊楠  我现在不能接电话
This is Shannan. I can't answer my phone right now
因为我要忙些更有趣的事情
because I'm doing something way more fun.
你有时候很混蛋  你知道吗
You can be a real asshole, you know that?
但是大家都听你的
But you're an asshole people listen to.
如果她们不听你的  你就自己干
And if they don't, you make 'em.
我做不到
I don't got what you got.
她也做不到  或者她  她们都做不到
Neither does she, or her, or any of us.
我们永远不可能成为年度最佳母亲  但是
We was never gonna be Mother of the Year, but...
考虑到当下
given the circumstances...
我支持你
you get my vote.
一\n\n\n年\n\n\n后
♪ 梦中佳人 ♪
♪ Beautiful dreamer ♪
♪ 在海上 ♪
♪ Out on the sea ♪
♪ 美人鱼吟唱着心中悲伤 ♪
♪ Mermaids are chanting The wild Lorelei ♪
♪ 在小河那边烟雾飘荡 ♪
♪ Over the streamlet vapors are born ♪
♪ 轻轻地等待着黎明来到 ♪
♪ Waiting to fade at the bright coming morn ♪
♪ 美丽的梦神  心灵之光 ♪
♪ Beautiful dreamer, beam on my heart... ♪
失踪
-喂  -是玛丽吗
- Hello? - Is this Mari?
-是  -我是乔·斯卡利斯
- Yes. - It's Joe Scalise.
橡树海滩的
From Oak Beach.
哈克特医生在卖他的房子
Dr. Hackett put his house up for sale.
那你该叫罗宾·里奇来
Well, great. Call Robin Leach.
罗宾·里奇是一档关于豪宅名车的节目的主持人
他已经收拾好行李了
His car is already packed.
他想一走了之
He's gonna disappear.
如果你还想和他谈谈  这是最后的机会了
If you ever want to talk to him, this could be your last chance.
此路
不通
你想聊聊
You wanna talk?
聊吧
Talk.
你已经毁了我的生活了
You've already upended my life.
你在暗示是我那晚追了那个女孩
You're implying I chased after this girl.
我自己走路都不利索
I can't catch up to myself walking backwards.
-是  但  -我年轻的时候
- Yes, but-- - When I was young,
被困在一只小艇上
I was... stranded on a skiff...
四面是水
in the water...
一片漆黑
in the dark.
只有我一个人
I was all alone
很害怕自己  会死
and scared I was... gonna die.
然后  我看到了一条船
Then I saw this boat.
离我很远  但是
It was far away, but...
\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h无粉
丁腈检查手套
我还是发射了照明弹
I sent up a flare,
他们来救我了
and they came to save me.
第二天
The next day,
我就报名了去学了急救医学
I enrolled in emergency medicine.
从那开始  我的专长就是
Ever since, my specialty has been...
救死扶伤
saving lives.
如果她还活着  我们会找她他的
If she's out there, we gotta find her.
你是个大英雄
You're the real hero.
一位为了女儿愿意付出一切的母亲
A mother who would go to any lengths for her daughter.
这是真正的英雄主义
That is true heroism.
吉尔伯特夫人
Mrs. Gilbert.
很高兴再见到你
Nice to see you again.
不要怕  我没带订书机来
Don't worry. I left my staple gun at home.
你怎么进来我办公室的
So how did you get in my office?
已经不是你的办公室了
It's not your office anymore.
对  是啊
True. True.
没错  他们是说要让我提前退休
Yeah, they're putting me out to pasture, as they say.
你觉得  世人会记住你什么
What do you think you'll be most remembered for?
你来干什么
What can I help you with?
你为什么不派人去搜沼泽
Why haven't you searched the marsh?
这是橡树海滩里  唯一没被搜的地方
It's the only place in Oak Beach you haven't searched.
因为一个成年男人都无法穿过那里
Because a grown man can't get through there,
更别提一个90多斤的小女孩了
never mind a 100-pound girl.
是  但那就是珊楠最后出现的安科路旁边
Yeah, but it borders Anchor Way where Shannan was last seen,
而且还挨着皮特·哈克特住着的左舷路
and Larboard Court where Peter Hackett lives.
所以  还是因为哈克特
Ah, so this is about Hackett.
我们已经判定他无罪了
We've already cleared him.
什么  你们得去跟乔·斯卡利斯聊聊
What... You gotta talk to Joe Scalise.
乔·斯卡利斯是个偏执的阴谋论者
Joe Scalise is a paranoid conspiracy freak.
他跟哈克特宿怨已久
He and Hackett hate each other.
他们很多年前就因为土地问题吵过架
Some dispute they had years ago over land.
他恨不得哈克特死
He wants to bury Hackett.
也许他在把你当枪使呢
Maybe he's giving you the shovel.
那她的外套怎么说
What about her jacket?
如果哈克特和珊楠接触过
If Hackett had contact with Shannan,
那她的外套可以证明
her jacket would prove it.
上面会有皮肤细胞或衣服纤维之类的吧
It would have skin cells or fibers on it or something.
我们没有那件外套
We don't have the jacket.
他们一开始捡到外套的时候
When they first picked it up,
珊楠的失踪还没有正式立案
Shannan wasn't officially missing
现在外套不见了
and it got lost.
这算什么  是在掩饰无能  还是甩脱责任
What is this, some kind of cover-up or just incompetence?
赶紧去搜沼泽  否则我就去找媒体了
Search the marsh or I'm going on the news.
理查德
退休快乐
海岸线
汽车旅馆
一年前  警方首次在海洋公园外的路边
A year ago, the police first discovered the remains
发现了被丢弃的三具尸体的遗骸
of three bodies dumped along the side of the road off Ocean Park.
-怎么了  -他们为了找那个妓女
- What's happening? - They're draining the marsh,
要清理这片沼泽
looking for that hooker.
玛丽
Mari!
洛兰
Lorraine.
-你在这里干什么  -来参加周年守夜的
- What are you doing here? - I came for the anniversary vigil.
其他人在来的路上
The others are on their way.
好了  别担心
Hey, don't worry.
我们不会让你一个人承受的  好吗
We're not gonna let you go through this alone. All right?
警方使用挖土机等重型机械
Heavy equipment, including a backhoe,
在浓密的灌木丛和沼泽中进行挖掘
were brought in to dig through the thick brush and marsh.
警察局长表示  这一带地形过于复杂
The commissioner says the area was too tough
搜查人员无法徒步搜查
for the searchers to get through on foot.
橡树海滩失踪的性工作者珊楠·吉尔伯特
Here in Oak Beach, missing sex worker, Shannan Gilbert,
最后一次被看到还活着
was last seen alive
是她正在离开顾客的房子的时候
leaving a client's house.
去年警方在寻找珊楠·吉尔伯特的过程中
During the search for Shannan Gilbert last year,
发现了四具尸体
four other bodies were discovered.
现在  是十具尸体了
There are now ten sets of remains,
其中还有一半尸体身份不明
half of whom are still unidentified.
据警方透露  珊楠·吉尔伯特的失踪
According to the police, Shannan Gilbert's disappearance
与这些尸体无关
is unrelated to those.
我们认为  珊楠·吉尔伯特在她失踪那晚
We believe that Shannan Gilbert ran into that area
跑到了这片区域
the night she disappeared.
她一定就在某处
She's in there someplace,
我们会尽全力去寻找她
and we're going to do everything we can to find her.
米西  谢谢你  真的  多亏了你
Thanks, Missy. Yeah, I owe you.
好了  回头见吧
Okay, see you soon.
米西会在来的路上接上她们
Missy's gonna pick up the girls on her way.
你手在抖
Your hands are shaking.
他们都说  知道好过什么都不知道
They say not knowing is worse than knowing,
我觉得未必
but I'm not so sure.
如果找到了她
And if they find her,
我就知道她死了
I know she's gone,
我还是会很愤怒
but I'll still be angry.
如果没找到她
And if they don't find her,
我就还有希望
I have hope.
没错  但你还是会愤怒
Yeah, but you're still angry.
我怎么才能不愤怒
How do I get rid of the anger?
等到你不再责备自己
Well, you stop blaming yourself.
这不是你的错
It's not your fault.
明白吗
Yeah?
-有发现了  -你发现什么了
- I think we got something! - What do you got down there?
-拿个相机过来  -马上隔离这一片
- Get a camera down here! - Rope this off right now!
-在那  -需要托架吗
- Over there. - We gonna need a cradle?
他们找到了什么
What did they find?
-我等会儿打回去  -给我看看  不
- I'll call you back. - Show me! No...
-让她过来吧  -别他妈挡着我
- Let her through. - Get the fuck out of my way!
-找到什么了  -让她过来
- What did they find? - Let her through.
找到什么了  那边是什么
What's over there? What's over there?
到底是什么
What is it?
快告诉我  他妈的  到底找到什么了
Tell me right now, goddamn it! What did you find?
求你了
Please!
长官
Officer.
珊楠·吉尔伯特
对不起
I'm sorry.
我会带你回家的
I'm gonna take you home.
今天  我们为了珊楠
As much as today is about Shannan,
也不只为了珊楠
it's not just about Shannan.
为了我们所有人
It's about all of us...
所有受这件事影响的
every one of us and our friends and family
亲人和朋友们
that were affected by this.
警方辜负了我们
The police failed us.
辜负了我们的孩子们
They failed every one of our girls.
警方没能在她们受到伤害时保护她们
They failed to keep them safe when they were at risk.
她们失踪时  警方也没有认真对待
They failed to take their disappearances seriously,
更没有抓住那些
and they failed to go after the people
伤害我们孩子的坏人
who took advantage of our girls.
警察内部  甚至就可能有这样的人
Some of them may even be those people.
他们无视了我
And they ignored me,
就像那晚无视珊楠的报警一样
just like they ignored Shannan the night she called for help
那晚一个小时后警察才到
and waited an hour for them to arrive.
为什么我们的女儿要遭受责备
Why are our girls to blame at the
而那些真正的坏人却无人怪罪
exclusion of everybody else?
是时候开始问责了  我愿意从自己开始
It's time for accountability, and I'm starting with myself.
回家吧
Let's go home.
珊楠·吉尔伯特遗体的独立尸检报告
与警方的珊楠死于恶劣环境的说法相矛盾
报告指出她的伤势与他杀勒死相符
没有证据表明她摄入过毒品
最终有10至16名受害者被认为是
洛纳岛连环杀手所为
本案没有嫌疑人受到指控
后续电话记录证实 皮特·哈克特确实给玛丽·吉尔伯特打过电话
她对他提起了非正常的死亡诉讼
这是我们在这的原因  我的女儿  珊楠
This is why we're here. This is my daughter, Shannan.
2016年\h2月
她不会被遗忘的
And she won't be forgotten.
她绝不会被忘记
She never will be forgotten.
必要的话
And we are gonna continue to fight
我们会一直坚持问责
as long as we need to...
直到能
until...
为我们的女儿们伸张正义
justice is done for our daughter.
2016年7月  玛丽的女儿莎拉因停止服用治疗精神分裂症药物后
精神病发作
♪ 清晨的呼唤在我耳边低语 ♪
♪ Morning calls with whispers in my ears ♪
玛丽试图阻止  但受到致命伤
♪ 你的灵魂伴我左右 ♪
♪ I believe the spirit is near ♪
♪ 日子静悄悄地一去不复返 ♪
♪ Days go quiet and disappear ♪
莎拉·吉尔伯特一直支持着珊楠
并继续为她伸张正义
♪ 我恐惧幽暗之处的真相 ♪
♪ Darkness knows the truth, I fear ♪
♪ 上天可鉴  我在尝试坚强 ♪
♪ God knows I've tried to stay strong ♪
♪ 我向上天的发誓总是徒劳 ♪
♪ I swear to God, I swear in vain ♪
♪ 我怒火中烧了太久 ♪
♪ Been raging and angry for so long ♪
电影改编自书籍
《失踪的女孩：一个悬而未决的美国之谜》
罗伯特·考尔克
♪ 独自守着我的伤痛 ♪
♪ Alone with all my pain ♪
♪ 只为给你一个甜蜜的开始 ♪
♪ Only to give you a sweet beginning ♪
♪ 但无论我多么努力 ♪
♪ But no matter how hard I try ♪
♪ 却都处在失败的边缘 ♪
♪ I find myself on the losing end ♪
♪ 生命中有太多难处 ♪
♪ Of all the trouble I'd in life ♪
♪ 你的不见  让我心神不宁 ♪
♪ You are missing, I am haunted ♪
♪ 当你已支离破碎  我却无所畏惧 ♪
♪ You're broken, but I am fearless ♪
♪ 你在听吗  我好需要你 ♪
♪ Are you listening? Cause you are wanted ♪
♪ 我凝听过你的诉说 ♪
♪ You've spoken, and I have heard ♪
♪ 每个夜晚  我都梦得到你 ♪
♪ In my dreams, I see you ♪
♪ 似乎  你也梦到了我 ♪
♪ And it seems you can see me too ♪
♪ 每个夜晚  我感觉到你 ♪
♪ In my dreams, I feel you ♪
♪ 好像  你也感觉得到我 ♪
♪ And it seems you can feel me too ♪
♪ 我会找到你的 ♪
♪ I will search for you ♪
♪ 无惧穿越风雨 ♪
♪ Through the wind and the rain ♪
♪ 我可能会倒下  但我绝不屈服 ♪
♪ I may bend, but I will never break ♪
♪ 如果痛苦是永恒的 ♪
♪ And if it hurts forever ♪
♪ 我也将一直承受 ♪
♪ I will live through the pain ♪
♪ 我会守在这里  带着痛苦倒下 ♪
♪ I will fall with the burden stand in its place ♪
♪ 在世界的每个角落寻找你 ♪
♪ I'll look for you on every corner ♪
♪ 在我走过的每一条街 ♪
♪ On every street I walk down ♪
♪ 我会永远心存希望 ♪
♪ I will never give up hoping ♪
♪ 终有一天我会将你找到 ♪
♪ That one day you will be found ♪
♪ 我也做过错误的选择 ♪
♪ I know I made some bad decisions ♪
♪ 我也犯过太多错 ♪
♪ And I got so much wrong ♪
♪ 现在我需要你的宽恕 ♪
♪ Now I need your forgiveness ♪
♪ 我要把你带回家 ♪
♪ Cause I'm coming to take you home ♪
♪ 在这邪恶世界的阴影之下 ♪
♪ In the shadows of a wicked world ♪
♪ 没有中心的盲目旋转 ♪
♪ Spinning without a sun ♪
♪ 可能我也只是一个失踪的女孩 ♪
♪ Maybe I was just another lost girl ♪
♪ 渴望着被发现 ♪
♪ Dying to be found ♪
♪ 在这邪恶世界的阴影之下 ♪
♪ In the shadows of a wicked world ♪
♪ 寻找你 ♪
♪ Looking for you ♪
♪ 可能我也只是一个失踪的女孩 ♪
♪ Maybe I was just another lost girl too ♪
♪ 在这邪恶世界的阴影之下 ♪
♪ In the shadows of a wicked world ♪
♪ 没有中心的盲目旋转 ♪
♪ Spinning without a sun ♪
♪ 可能我也只是一个失踪的女孩 ♪
♪ Maybe I was just another lost girl ♪
♪ 渴望着被发现 ♪
♪ Dying to be found ♪
♪ 可能我也只是一个失踪的女孩 ♪
♪ Maybe I was just another lost girl ♪
♪ 渴望着被发现 ♪
♪ Dying to be found ♪
♪ 可能我也只是一个失踪的女孩 ♪
♪ Maybe I was just another lost girl ♪
♪ 渴望着被发现 ♪
♪ Dying to be found ♪